MARCIN LIBELT

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

0048 785 275 027

marcin.libelt@gmail.com

marcin-libelt →

marcin-libelt →

Gdynia, Poland / Worldwide

LANGUAGES

Polish Native
English Full professional proficiency

EDUCATION

12.2015

MAGENTO CERTIFICATION - #0G0DUS04EC

2005-2008

Gdańska Wyższa Szkoła Humanistyczna, Gdańsk, Poland

DZIENNIKARSTWO, studia licencjackie

WORKING WITH

ReactJs JavaScript / TypeScript

NextJs GraphQL TailwindCss RWD

Jira Web Accessibility

Design Tokens GIT

Css3 GitHub / GitLab
Sass / Less BitBucket
HTML5 Linux

HIML5 LINU

FAMILIAR WITH

PWA PHP Magento MvSQL

VueJs UX / UI design

AlpineJs Figma

Docker Adobe XD

Laravel

HOBBIES

Tennis Cycling
Hiking Jogging
Molkky Travelling

PROFILE

A driven **Front-End Developer**, who thrives on delivering high-end solutions for clients. Gained more than 8 years of professional experience at building e-commerce websites based on Magento for famous fashion brands, but in recent years has become interested in **ReactJs** and modern technologies. Previously, for many years, coded as a hobby and on a freelance basis in **JS**, **PHP**, **HTML** and **CSS**. Today - has a strong understanding of design principles and how to apply them to the web. A guardian of the cleanliness, quality of the code and the accessibility of solutions for people with disabilities. A great team player willing to share knowledge with the team. Has a good communication skill, ability to speak and write freely in English. A fast learner who is always seeking opportunities and learning possibilities. Currently is working with **ReactJs**, **TypeScript** and **TailwindCss** - and would like to develop a career in them.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER - FREELANCE

07.2017 - PRESENT

LUMOS IT - SELF-EMPLOYMENT

Ogdynia, Poland

- creating websites and solutions for own clients using the ReactJs stack / Gatsby + Strapi
- cooperation with Movade in the field of assistance in implementing the website code in ReactJs technology
- cooperation with Alekseon Sp. z o.o. in implementation of the functionality of the cardboard packaging system for the warehouse ReactJs
- cooperation in building a CRM project in the stack: Laravel Jetstream + Inertia (VueJs 2)
- cooperation in maintaining projects based on Magento 2

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

05.2015 - 07.2017

ALEKSEON SP. Z O. O.

Ogdynia, Poland

- implementing the front end and maintaining projects based on Magento for luxury brands such as Manolo Blahnik, Christian Louboutin, Łukasz Jemioł, Horyzont
- adapting websites for users with disabilities experience in web accessibility A/AA
- working in Agile software development
- enhancing good practices in the company such as code review
- liaison with a business client on a daily basis
- management of a development team: mentoring, code review, internal training,

UX quality control, creating and assigning tickets in JIRA

- responsible for the hiring process of front-end developers - preparing recruitment tasks and verification of the given solutions

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

09.2009 - 05.2015

BAOBAZ POLAND SP. Z O. O.

Sopot, Poland

- developing and maintaining variety of Magento projects
- engaging new employees in internal development processes
- working within multinational team
- implementing html templates and newsletters

WEBMASTER

09.2008 - 05.2009

ARTNET SP. Z O. O.

O Gdańsk, Poland

- HTML/CSS implementation

- PHP coding
- creating PostgreSQL queries

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.